Performing, who knows, from his new album, Son of Spurgy, please welcome Daniel Caesar!
-♪ I'd probably be a waste of your time, but who knows?
♪
Chances are I'll step out of line, but who knows?
Lately, you've set up in my mind.
Yeah, girl, you and I like that.
Ooh.
Lately, I've been thinking that perhaps I am
Hiding in the disguise of an ever giving flower Incompetent steward of all of that sweet, sweet power Yesterday was feeling so good Now it's calling
I feel like that always if I could.
Is that wrong?
Tell me about the city you're from.
Is it hot?
Does it snow there?
Me by my side, my girl, my shooter Who's to say who calculates?
Not me, I'm no computer Is it?
A crime to be unsure In time we'll find If it's sustainable You're pure, you're kind Mature, divine You might be too good for me
think i'll take that thought to the grave but who knows i know that i love you always yeah girl you and i'd like that
Come on!
That's how you do it right there.
Come on, Daniel Caesar!
Son of Spurgey is out now.
We'll be right back, everybody.