Performing, who knows, from his new album, Son of Spurgy, please welcome Daniel Caesar!
I'll probably be a waste of your time, but who knows?
Chances are I'll step out of line, but who knows?
Lately, you've set up in my mind.
Yeah, girl, you and I like that.
Ooh.
Lately, I've been thinking that perhaps I
Hiding in the disguise of an ever-giving flower Incompetent steward of all of that sweet, sweet power Yesterday was feeling so good Now it's gone
I feel like that always if I could.
Is that wrong?
Tell me about the city you're from.
Is it hot?
Does it snow there?
Lately I've been thinking about my precarious
future will you be there with me by my side my girl my shooter who's to say who can't you ladies not me I'm no computer
Is it a crime to be unsure?
In time, we'll find if it's sustainable.
You're pure, you're kind, mature, divine.
You might be too good for me, unattainable.
Maybe we'll get married one day, but who knows?
I think I'll take that thought to the grave, but who knows?
I know that I'll love you always, yeah girl you and I'd like that.
Come on!
That's how you do it right there!
Come on, Daniel Caesar!
Son of Spurgey is out now!
We'll be right back, everybody!